Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: wear jewellery,
wear clothes,
carry a bag,
carry a baby
Narrator: 8
Speaker 2: win a match,
win a medal,
win a prize,
earn a salary,
earn money
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: know somebody well,
know something,
meet somebody for the first time,
meet at eleven o’clock
Narrator: 1
Speaker 2: hope that something good will happen,
hope to do something,
wait for a bus,
wait for a long time
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: watch TV,
watch a match,
look at a photo,
look at your watch
Narrator: 11
Speaker 2: look happy,
look about twenty-five years old,
look like your mother,
look like a model
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: miss the bus,
miss a class,
lose a match,
lose your glasses
Narrator: 9
Speaker 2: bring your dictionary,
bring something back from holiday,
take an umbrella,
take your children to school
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: look for your glasses,
look for a job,
find your glasses,
find a job
Narrator: 10
Speaker 2: say sorry,
say hello,
say something to somebody,
tell a joke,
tell a lie,
tell somebody something
Narrator: 7
Speaker 1: lend money to somebody,
borrow money from somebody
Narrator: 1
Speaker 2: hear a noise,
hear the door bell,
listen to music,
listen to the radio